[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest crocodilian in Africa?", "correct_answer": "Nile crocodile", "incorrect_answers": ["Gharial", "Slender-snouted Crocodile", "Saltwater crocodile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The period of time between maximum and minimum sunspot activity, known as the Solar Cycle is about how many years in length?", "correct_answer": "11 years", "incorrect_answers": ["51 years", "101 years", "1 year"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of the color sangria comes from the Spanish word sangre. What does it mean?", "correct_answer": "Blood", "incorrect_answers": ["Wine", "Sorrow", "Tear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tomas Transtrmer, Assia Djebar and Raja Rao have won one, what is it?", "correct_answer": "Neustadt International Prize for Literature", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobbitt National Prize for Poetry", "Pulitzer Prize for Poetry", "Nobel Prize in Literature"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor plays Mac MacGuff in Juno. He is Spidermans boss in the Spiderman movies and a shrink on Law and Order.", "correct_answer": "J.K. Simmons", "incorrect_answers": ["Rainn Wilson", "Daniel Clark", "Michael Cera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fungi and their products are involved in the process of production of which of these goods?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Detergents", "Opiates", "Antibiotics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is part of the brainstem, a stalk of the brain below the celebral hemispsheres?", "correct_answer": "pons", "incorrect_answers": ["neocortex", "telecephanon", "hypothalamus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dont Be a Menace to South Central While Drinking Your Juice in the Hood, what does Loc Dog have sticking out of his top braid?", "correct_answer": "an antenna", "incorrect_answers": ["a bag", "pen", "a pacifier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Norbit, who is Rasputias oldest brother?", "correct_answer": "Big Black Jack", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue", "Earl", "Freddie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What astronomical object was named in honor of Greek philosopher Aristotle?", "correct_answer": "A crater on the Moon", "incorrect_answers": ["A star", "A constellation", "One of the rings of Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gatorade, a non-carbonated sports drink, was invented by researchers at the University of Florida and named in honor of the Florida Gators, the schools football team.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tooth enamel is the hardest substance in the body.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]